<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yusuf</title>
    <link>https://wyusufa.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yusuf</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wyusufa.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2D ArrayList in Java</title>
      <link>https://wyusufa.github.io/posts/two-d-array-java/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wyusufa.github.io/posts/two-d-array-java/</guid>
      <description>Each time i am working with 2D arraylist in Java, I always google it and it takes a while to find the simplest implementation. Rather than spend a few minutes in the future each time i have to implement 2D arraylist in Java, i rather write it down.
Here it is :
List&amp;lt;List&amp;lt;Integer&amp;gt;&amp;gt; arr = new ArrayList&amp;lt;&amp;gt;(); arr.add(Arrays.asList(1,2,3)); arr.add(Arrays.asList(4,5,6)); arr.add(Arrays.asList(9,8,9)); Projectsss : ddddd spring-boot dfdf</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Sublime in Git Bash (Windows)</title>
      <link>https://wyusufa.github.io/posts/integrate-sublime-in-gitbash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wyusufa.github.io/posts/integrate-sublime-in-gitbash/</guid>
      <description>the default terminal in git bash is vim. We can change it to sublime.
 open change editor section in git docs scroll down to Sublime Text (Windows 64-bit). Copy the git command on the right : git config --global core.editor &amp;quot;&#39;C:\Program Files\Sublime Text\sublime_text.exe&#39; -w&amp;quot;. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to change the sublime text directory path according to where you install sublime text in your machine.  after this, everytime you want to change commit message by typing git commit, the sublime text editor will be opened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Static Website With Hugo and Github Pages </title>
      <link>https://wyusufa.github.io/posts/tutorial-hugo-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wyusufa.github.io/posts/tutorial-hugo-blog/</guid>
      <description>introduction A static website is one with stable content where every user sees the exact same thing on each individual page. There are tools to build static website, such as wordpress, hugo, jekyll, etc. In this tutorial i want to explain how to use Hugo to build static website. After you build the static website, you need to host it online. There are many services that help you to host your website online, either paid or free, such as netlify, github pages, heroku, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://wyusufa.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wyusufa.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Wanda Yusuf Alvian =&amp;gt; [Github | CV | Linkedin | HackerRank]
java springboot SQL javascript python
what i do at the moment :
 backend engineer intern @investree indonesia enroll in IDCamp backend bootcamp enroll in jetbrain academy prepare for tech interview (DSA). My favorite resources : hackerrank.com, cracking coding interview (book), and elements of programming interview (book) learning about database, SQL, and anything related to backend looking for a job as software engineer (backend)  I believe that a good programmer is someone who can master any technology quickly to solve problem using computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://wyusufa.github.io/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wyusufa.github.io/project/</guid>
      <description>Code repository, Code documentation, and Explanation in README
hello-world-springboot [springboot, java] return JSON &amp;ldquo;hello world&amp;rdquo; in browser using HTTP GET using springboot, understand how to create springboot app and run it. Learn about how to getting start with springboot</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
