<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Some Title</title>
    <link>https://wyusufa.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Some Title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wyusufa.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Sublime in Git Bash (Windows)</title>
      <link>https://wyusufa.github.io/posts/integrate-sublime-in-gitbash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wyusufa.github.io/posts/integrate-sublime-in-gitbash/</guid>
      <description>the default terminal in git bash is vim. We can change it to sublime.
 open change editor section in git docs scroll down to Sublime Text (Windows 64-bit). Copy the git command on the right : git config --global core.editor &amp;quot;&#39;C:\Program Files\Sublime Text\sublime_text.exe&#39; -w&amp;quot;. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to change the sublime text directory path according to where you install sublime text in your machine.  after this, everytime you want to change commit message by typing git commit, the sublime text editor will be opened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Static Website With Hugo and Github Pages </title>
      <link>https://wyusufa.github.io/posts/tutorial-hugo-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wyusufa.github.io/posts/tutorial-hugo-blog/</guid>
      <description>introduction A static website is one with stable content where every user sees the exact same thing on each individual page. There are tools to build static website, such as wordpress, hugo, jekyll, etc. In this tutorial i want to explain how to use Hugo to build static website. After you build the static website, you need to host it online. There are many services that help you to host your website online, either paid or free, such as netlify, github pages, heroku, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://wyusufa.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wyusufa.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About me CV | Linkedin | Github | HackerRank | Youtube
My name is Wanda Yusuf Alvian (nickname : Yusuf) and I am a self taught programmer.
My main interest is building backend system using java. I have experience using javascript, python, and C# in the past.
I believe that a good programmer is someone who can master any technology fast to solve problem using computer. To be that kind of programmer, someone must to have good fundamental knowledge, problem solving skill, communication skill, and self learning skill.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
